Guide to the Clark E. Warburton papers, 1920-1979
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Clark E. Warburton papers
1920-1979
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Clark E. Warburton, 1896-1976
C0110
161.25 linear feet (117 boxes)
The collection consists of correspondence, published and unpublished Warburton manuscripts (such as Warburtion's unpublished history of monetary disequilibrium), printed matter, and subject files.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Collection donated by Clark E. Warburton in 1979.
Biographical Information
Born in Shady Grove, New York on January 27, 1896, Clark E. Warburton taught at several colleges and universities in the United States and India before joining the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) in 1934. He eventually became Chief of the Banking and Business Section of the Division of Research and Statistics. He retained that post until his retirement in 1965. Throughout his career, Warburton was well known for his support of the theory that monetary forces are the key cause of economic disturbances. He made numerous contributions to economics scholarship and practices during his long career.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of correspondence, published and unpublished Warburton manuscripts (such as Warburtion's unpublished history of monetary disequilibrium), printed matter, and subject files.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically and chronologically by subject.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives created a digital collection about the hosted by GMU Libraries in 2008.
holds additional Clark Warburon papers in Record Group 34: Records of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1920-1993.
Index Terms
Persons:
Warburton, Clark, b. 1896.
Corporate Names:
Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation.
Subjects:
Banks and banking--United States.; Economics--United States.; Finance--United States.
Contents List
- Clark Warburton Papers
  - Abramovitz, Moses (Folder 1, Box 1)
  - Adams, E. Sherman (Folder 2, Box 1)
  - Adams, Sherman (Folder 3, Box 1)
  - Agger, E. E. (Folder 4, Box 1)
  - Agriculture, U.S Dept. (Folder 5, Box 1)
  - Ahearn, Frank (Folder 6, Box 1)
  - Norman Albrecht (Folder 7, Box 1)
  - Alden, F. Charles (Folder 8, Box 1)
  - Alexander, S. Sidney (Folder 9, Box 1)
  - M. Allais (Folder 10, Box 1)
  - Allen, R. William (Folder 11, Box 1)
  - Amberg, V. Harold (Folder 12, Box 1)
  - American Academy of Political and Social Science (Folder 13, Box 1)
  - American Assembly (Columbia University) (Folder 14, Box 1)
  - American Association of University Professors (Folder 15, Box 1)
  - The American Banker (Folder 16, Box 1)
  - The American Banker Association (Folder 17, Box 1)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Folder 18, Box 1)
  - American College Bureau (Folder 19, Box 1)
  - American Consular Service- Calcutta (Folder 20, Box 1)
  - American Investors Union (Folder 21, Box 1)
  - The American Journal of Economics and Sociology (Folder 22, Box 1)
  - American Statistical Association (Folder 23, Box 1)
  - American University (Folder 24, Box 1)
  - Anderson, M. Benjamin (Folder 25, Box 1)
  - Clay J. Anderson (Folder 26, Box 1)
  - Anderson, John T. (Folder 27, Box 1)
  - M. D. Anderson (Folder 28, Box 1)
  - William M. Anderson (Folder 29, Box 1)
  - Angell, James W. (Folder 30, Box 1)
  - Annalist (Folder 31, Box 1)
  - Annals (Folder 32, Box 1)
  - Armstrong, G. S. (Folder 33, Box 1)
  - Arndt, E. R. (Folder 34, Box 1)
  - Joseph Aschheim (Folder 35, Box 1)
  - Association of Reserve City Bankers (Folder 36, Box 1)
  - Association Against The Prohibition Amendment (Folder 37, Box 1)
  - Thomas B. Atkinson (Folder 38, Box 1)
  - Atlantic Monthly (Folder 39, Box 1)
  - Auble, Arthur G. (Folder 40, Box 1)
  - Ayres, Clarence (Folder 41, Box 1)
  - Ayres, Leonard P. (Folder 42, Box 1)
  - A-Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 43, Box 1)
  - A- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 44, Box 1)
  - A- Miscellaneous 1932-54 (Folder 45, Box 1)
  - Bach, G.L. (Folder 46, Box 1)
  - Badger, Sherwin C. (Folder 47, Box 1)
  - Balbach, Anatol (Folder 48, Box 1)
  - Banking and Currency Committee (Folder 49, Box 1)
  - Barber, Clarence L. (Folder 50, Box 1)
  - Barger, Harold (Folder 51, Box 1)
  - Barr, E.C. (Folder 52, Box 1)
  - Barrons (Folder 53, Box 1)
  - Bassie, Lewis V. (Folder 54, Box 1)
  - Batcheller, Hiland G. (Folder 55, Box 1)
  - Baumol, William J. (Folder 56, Box 1)
  - Becker, Arthur P. (Folder 57, Box 1)
  - Becker, Gary S. (Folder 58, Box 1)
  - Beckhart, B.H. (Folder 59, Box 1)
  - Beckwith, Burnham (Folder 60, Box 1)
  - Bell, Prof. James Washington (Folder 61, Box 1)
  - Bell, Spurgeon (Folder 62, Box 1)
  - Benner, Claude L. (Folder 63, Box 1)
  - Bennet, Wallace F. (Folder 64, Box 1)
  - Benson, Ezra (Folder 65, Box 1)
  - Bernstein, Edward M. (Folder 66, Box 1)
  - Berry, Thomas (Folder 67, Box 1)
  - Bezanson, Anne (Folder 68, Box 1)
  - Bieri, Hermann (Folder 69, Box 1)
  - Biggs, E. Earl (Folder 70, Box 1)
  - Black, John D. (Folder 71, Box 1)
  - Blackburn, Alice (Folder 72, Box 1)
  - Blakey, Roy G. (Folder 73, Box 1)
  - Blough, Roy (Folder 74, Box 1)
  - Bohn, Frank (Folder 75, Box 1)
  - Boothe, Armistead L. (Folder 76, Box 1)
  - Booz, Allen and Hamilton (Folder 77, Box 1)
  - Bopp, Karl R. (Folder 78, Box 1)
  - Bowman, R.T. (Folder 79, Box 1)
  - Bowman, Ward S. ,Jr. (Folder 80, Box 1)
  - Bradford, William C. (Folder 81, Box 1)
  - Breamen, John (Folder 82, Box 1)
  - Bratt, Elmer C. (Folder 83, Box 1)
  - Bratter, Herbert M. (Folder 84, Box 1)
  - Bready, Richard H. (Folder 85, Box 1)
  - Brill, Daniel H. (Folder 86, Box 1)
  - Bronfenbrenner, Martin (Folder 87, Box 1)
  - Brookings Institution (Folder 88, Box 1)
  - Brown, Cary E. (Folder 89, Box 1)
  - Brown, Harry Gunnison Brown, Elizabeth Read (Folder 90, Box 1)
  - Brown, Leo S., ESQ (Folder 91, Box 1)
  - Brown, Phillips H. (Folder 92, Box 1)
  - Brown University, Library (Folder 93, Box 1)
  - Brown, William A., Jr. (Folder 94, Box 1)
  - Brundage, Percival F. (Folder 95, Box 1)
  - Bryan, Malcolm (Folder 96, Box 1)
  - Buchanan, D.H. (Folder 97, Box 1)
  - Buechel, Henry T. (Folder 98, Box 1)
  - Budget, Bureau of (Folder 99, Box 1)
  - Burger, John (General Mills Inc.) (Folder 100, Box 1)
  - Burgess, Randolph W. (Folder 101, Box 1)
  - Burns, Arthur E. (Folder 102, Box 1)
  - Burr, Susan S. (Folder 103, Box 1)
  - Bye, Raymond T. (Folder 104, Box 1)
  - B- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 105, Box 1)
  - B- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 106, Box 1)
  - B- Miscellaneous 1932-55 (Folder 108, Box 1)
  - Cadle, Austin (Folder 108, Box 1)
  - Calkins, Robert D. (Folder 109, Box 1)
  - Canadian Journal of Economics and Political Science (Folder 110, Box 1)
  - Capehart, Homer E. (Folder 111, Box 1)
  - Carman, Harry J. (Folder 112, Box 1)
  - Carr, Hobart C. (Folder 113, Box 1)
  - Carroll, Mollie R. (Folder 114, Box 1)
  - Carson, William J. (Folder 115, Box 1)
  - Caskey, Wayne F. (Folder 116, Box 1)
  - Catchings, Waddill (Folder 117, Box 1)
  - Cella, Francis R. (Folder 118, Box 1)
  - Central Hanover Bank and Trust Co. (Folder 119, Box 1)
  - Chalfont, Ella I. (Folder 120, Box 1)
  - Chandler, Lester (Folder 121, Box 1)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank (Folder 122, Box 1)
  - Cheadle, Harold L. (Folder 123, Box 1)
  - Chevalier, Willard (Folder 124, Box 1)
  - Clague, Ewan (Folder 125, Box 1)
  - Clark, Colin (Folder 126, Box 1)
  - Clark, Georgia N. (Folder 127, Box 1)
  - Clark, John M. (Folder 128, Box 1)
  - Clemence, Richard V. (Folder 129, Box 1)
  - Cleveland, W.C. (Folder 130, Box 1)
  - Cloos, George W. (Folder 131, Box 1)
  - Clyman, Bernard (Folder 132, Box 1)
  - Cohen, Morris (Folder 133, Box 1)
  - Cole, Arthur H. (Folder 134, Box 1)
  - Collard, C.G. (Folder 135, Box 1)
  - Collier's Na. Weekly (Folder 136, Box 1)
  - Colm, Yerhard (Folder 137, Box 1)
  - Columbia University (Folder 138, Box 1)
  - Columbia University Studies in History, Economics and Public Law (Folder 139, Box 1)
  - Commerce, U.S. Department (Folder 140, Box 1)
  - Commission on Money and Credit (Folder 141, Box 1)
  - Cone, Frederick M. (Folder 142, Box 1)
  - Constantacatos, M. E. (Folder 143, Box 1)
  - Cornelius, S. (Folder 144, Box 1)
  - Consumers Union (Folder 145, Box 1)
  - Copeland, Morris (Folder 146, Box 1)
  - Cornell University (Folder 147, Box 1)
  - Cortney, Philip (Folder 148, Box 1)
  - Court, Andrew T. (Folder 149, Box 1)
  - Cover, John H. (Folder 150, Box 1)
  - Cowherd, R. G. (Folder 151, Box 1)
  - Cowles Commission for Research in Economics (Folder 152, Box 1)
  - Cox, Reavis (Folder 153, Box 1)
  - Crawford, Hon. Frederick (Folder 154, Box 1)
  - Creamer, Daniel (Folder 155, Box 1)
  - Crews, Joseph S. (Folder 156, Box 1)
  - Crawther, Geoffrey (Folder 157, Box 1)
  - Cruikshank, George E. (Folder 158, Box 1)
  - Crum, W.L. (Folder 159, Box 1)
  - Culbertson, J.M (Folder 160, Box 1)
  - Cummings, Frederick (Folder 161, Box 1)
  - Currie, Lauchlin (Folder 162, Box 1)
  - C- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 163, Box 1)
  - C- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 164, Box 1)
  - C- Miscellaneous 1932-49 (Folder 165, Box 1)
  - Clarence H. Danhof (Folder 166, Box 1)
  - Dauer, Ernst A. (Folder 167, Box 1)
  - Davenport, Donald H. (Folder 168, Box 1)
  - Davenport, Herbert J. (Folder 169, Box 1)
  - Davis, J.S. (Folder 170, Box 1)
  - Dean, Charles (Folder 171, Box 1)
  - Dean, Joel (Folder 172, Box 1)
  - Deeds, Allan K. (Folder 173, Box 1)
  - Delano, Preston (Folder 174, Box 1)
  - Delano, Frederic A. (Folder 175, Box 1)
  - Despres, Emile (Folder 176, Box 1)
  - Dewhurst, Frederic J. (Folder 177, Box 1)
  - Dickinson, Frank G. (Folder 178, Box 1)
  - Dillard, Dudley (Folder 179, Box 1)
  - Dince, Robert R. (Folder 180, Box 1)
  - Dischamps, J.C. (Folder 181, Box 1)
  - Doblin, Ernest M. (Folder 182, Box 1)
  - Dorfman, Joseph (Folder 183, Box 1)
  - Douglas, Paul H. (Folder 184, Box 1)
  - Dowrie, George W. (Folder 185, Box 1)
  - Draper, Ernest G. (Federal Reserve System) (Folder 186, Box 1)
  - Dublin, Jack (Folder 187, Box 1)
  - Du Brul, S.M. (Folder 188, Box 1)
  - Dunkman, W.E. (Folder 189, Box 1)
  - Dunn, Edgar S. (Folder 190, Box 1)
  - Dun's Review (Folder 191, Box 1)
  - Dyason, John (Folder 192, Box 1)
  - D- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 193, Box 1)
  - D- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 194, Box 1)
  - D- Miscellaneous 1932-41 (Folder 195, Box 1)
  - The Econometric Institute (Folder 196, Box 1)
  - Eastburn, David P. (Folder 197, Box 1)
  - The Econometric Society (Folder 198, Box 1)
  - The Economic and Business Foundation (Folder 199, Box 1)
  - Economic Journal (Folder 200, Box 1)
  - Eddy, George (Folder 201, Box 1)
  - Edwards, Corvin D. (Folder 202, Box 1)
  - Eisner, Robert (Folder 203, Box 1)
  - Elliot, D.C. (Folder 204, Box 1)
  - Ellis, Howard S. (Folder 205, Box 1)
  - Ellis, Paul W. (Folder 206, Box 1)
  - Elliston, Herbert (Folder 207, Box 1)
  - Emden, Paul H. (Folder 208, Box 1)
  - Emory University (Folder 209, Box 1)
  - Encyclopaedia of the Social Sciences (Folder 210, Box 1)
  - Ensley, Grover W. (Folder 211, Box 1)
  - Epstein, Lillian (Folder 212, Box 1)
  - Estadistica (Folder 213, Box 1)
  - Evans, Mercer G. (Folder 214, Box 1)
  - Evans, Griffith C. (Folder 215a, Box 1)
  - Evans, Joseph E. (Wall Street Journal) (Folder 215b, Box 1)
  - Evans, O.L (Folder 215c, Box 1)
  - Evans, R.M (Folder 216, Box 1)
  - Eveland, DeForest (Folder 217, Box 1)
  - E- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 218, Box 1)
  - E- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 219, Box 1)
  - E- Miscellaneous 1932-44 (Folder 220, Box 1)
  - Mordecai Ezekiel (Folder 221, Box 1)
  - Farley, James A. (Folder 222, Box 1)
  - Fenderson, A.D. (Folder 223, Box 1)
  - Ferger, Wirth (Folder 224, Box 1)
  - Finney, Katherine (Folder 225, Box 1)
  - The First Boston Corporation (Folder 226, Box 1)
  - Fisher, Irving (Folder 227, Box 1)
  - Fisher, J.H. (Folder 228, Box 1)
  - Fisher, Halder W. (Folder 229, Box 1)
  - Fitch, Lyle C. (Folder 230, Box 1)
  - Fitzgerald, A.C. (Folder 231, Box 1)
  - Fitzpatrick, Paul J. (Folder 232, Box 1)
  - Flanders, Ralph E. (Folder 232, Box 1)
  - Ford Foundation (Folder 234, Box 1)
  - Ford Foundation Research Project and Others (Folder 235, Box 1)
  - Foreign Affairs (Folder 236, Box 1)
  - Foreign Press Service (Folder 237, Box 1)
  - Foreman, Clark (Folder 238, Box 1)
  - Fortune (Folder 239, Box 1)
  - Foulke, Roy A. (Folder 240, Box 1)
  - Foundation for Economic Education (Folder 241, Box 1)
  - Fraine, Harold G. (Folder 242, Box 1)
  - Friedman, Elisha M. (Folder 1, Box 2)
  - Irwin Friend (Folder 2, Box 2)
  - Friendly, Alfred (Folder 3, Box 2)
  - David Frank (Folder 4, Box 2)
  - F- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 5, Box 2)
  - F- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 6, Box 2)
  - F- Miscellaneous 1932-46 (Folder 7, Box 2)
  - Gaier, Sidney R. (Folder 8, Box 2)
  - Gainsbrugh, M.R. (Folder 9, Box 2)
  - Galbraith, J.A. (Folder 10, Box 2)
  - Gallman, Robert (Folder 11, Box 2)
  - Galloway, George B. (Folder 12, Box 2)
  - Gasparini, Innocenzo (Folder 13, Box 2)
  - Capt. Cecial Aubrey Gasque (Folder 14, Box 2)
  - Gebhart, John C. (Folder 15, Box 2)
  - General Motors Corporation (Folder 16, Box 2)
  - Gilbert, Milton (Folder 17, Box 2)
  - Gleason, Allen H. (Folder 18, Box 2)
  - Golden, Clinton S. (Folder 19, Box 2)
  - Goldenweiser, E.A. (Folder 20, Box 2)
  - Goldsmith, Raymonf W. (Folder 21, Box 2)
  - Goodbar, Joseph E. (Folder 22, Box 2)
  - Goode, Richard (Folder 23, Box 2)
  - Goodrich, Carter (Folder 24, Box 2)
  - Gordon, William D. (Folder 25, Box 2)
  - Gordon, R. A. (Folder 26, Box 2)
  - Graham, Benjamin (Folder 27, Box 2)
  - Graham, Frank D. (Folder 28, Box 2)
  - Graue, Erwin (Folder 29, Box 2)
  - Gray, Peter H. (Folder 30, Box 2)
  - Grayson, Louis J. (Folder 31, Box 2)
  - Greensides, Neil G. (Folder 32, Box 2)
  - Greer, Guy (Folder 33, Box 2)
  - Gross, Bertram M. (Folder 34, Box 2)
  - Groves, Harold M. (Folder 35, Box 2)
  - Gulick, Luther (Folder 36, Box 2)
  - G- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 37, Box 2)
  - G- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 38, Box 2)
  - G- Miscellaneous 1932-43 (Folder 39, Box 2)
  - Hagen, Everett E. (Folder 40, Box 2)
  - Halbert, LeRoy A. (Folder 41, Box 2)
  - Haley, Bernard F. (Folder 42, Box 2)
  - Halm, George N. (Folder 43, Box 2)
  - Halvorson, Lloyd C. (Folder 44, Box 2)
  - Hamberg, D. (Folder 45, Box 2)
  - Hamilton, Walton H. (Folder 46, Box 2)
  - Hansen, Alvin H. (Folder 47, Box 2)
  - Hardy, Charles O. (Folder 48, Box 2)
  - Harmon, Elmer M. (Folder 49, Box 2)
  - Harper's Magazine (Folder 50, Box 2)
  - Harris, Seymour E. (Folder 51, Box 2)
  - Harrod, Roy (Folder 52, Box 2)
  - Harvard Business Review (Folder 53, Box 2)
  - Harvard University Press (Folder 54, Box 2)
  - Hastings, Hudson B. (Folder 55, Box 2)
  - Hauge, Gabriel (Folder 56, Box 2)
  - Hauser, Philip M. (Folder 57, Box 2)
  - Haywood, Chas F. (Folder 58, Box 2)
  - Haves, Elizabeth (Folder 59, Box 2)
  - Hayes, Samuel P., Jr. (Folder 60, Box 2)
  - Hazelett, Richard (Folder 61, Box 2)
  - Heimann, Edward (Folder 62, Box 2)
  - Heilperin, Michael A. (Folder 63, Box 2)
  - Hellborn, Ludwig S. (Folder 64, Box 2)
  - Hendershot, Ralph (Folder 65, Box 2)
  - Hendrick, Paul (Folder 66, Box 2)
  - Henderson, Leon (Folder 67, Box 2)
  - Herring, John P. (Folder 68, Box 2)
  - Heyman, Joseph K. (Folder 69, Box 2)
  - Hickernell, Warren F. (Folder 70, Box 2)
  - Hicks, Earl (Folder 71, Box 2)
  - Hildreth, Clifford (Folder 72, Box 2)
  - Hirsch, Julius (Folder 73, Box 2)
  - Hoad, William (Folder 74, Box 2)
  - Hoag, C.G. (Folder 75, Box 2)
  - Hobby, Oreta Culp (Folder 76, Box 2)
  - Hodgman, Donald R. (Folder 77, Box 2)
  - Hoffman, Dorothy B. (Sec. to Gov. Vardaman, FRS) (Folder 78, Box 2)
  - Holden, Arthur C. (Folder 79, Box 2)
  - Holland, Daniel m. (Folder 80, Box 2)
  - Henry Holt and Company (Folder 81, Box 2)
  - Homan, Paul T. (Folder 82, Box 2)
  - Hoover, Calvin B. (Folder 83, Box 2)
  - Hoover, Glenn E. (Folder 84, Box 2)
  - Hopkins, R.L. (Folder 85, Box 2)
  - Horwich, George (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Hoselitz, Bert F. (Folder 87, Box 2)
  - Hotelling, Harold (Folder 88, Box 2)
  - Howard, Eleanor (Folder 89, Box 2)
  - Hoyt, Elizabeth E. (Folder 90, Box 2)
  - Humphreys, George M. (Folder 91, Box 2)
  - Hunt, Edward E. (Folder 92, Box 2)
  - Hutt, W.H. (Folder 93, Box 2)
  - H- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 94, Box 2)
  - H- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 95, Box 2)
  - H- Miscellaneous 1932-60 (Folder 96, Box 2)
  - Innis, Harold L. (Folder 97, Box 2)
  - International Monetary Fund Library (Folder 98, Box 2)
  - Institute of Life Insurance (Folder 99, Box 2)
  - William Iselin and Co., Inc. (Folder 100, Box 2)
  - Ives, Irwing M. (Folder 101, Box 2)
  - I- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 102, Box 2)
  - I- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 103, Box 2)
  - I- Miscellaneous 1932-43 (Folder 104, Box 2)
  - Jackson, Gardner (Folder 105, Box 2)
  - Jackson, J. Hugh (Folder 106, Box 2)
  - Jacobson, Per (Folder 107, Box 2)
  - Jacoby, Neil H. (Folder 108, Box 2)
  - Jeffe, William (Folder 109, Box 2)
  - James, F. Cyril (Folder 110, Box 2)
  - James, Harlean (Folder 111, Box 2)
  - Jaszi, George (Folder 112, Box 2)
  - John, Tewkes (Folder 113, Box 2)
  - Johnson, Gale D. (Folder 114, Box 2)
  - Johnson, E.C. (Folder 115, Box 2)
  - Johnson, Edgar H. (Folder 116, Box 2)
  - Johnson, Harry G. (Folder 117, Box 2)
  - Johnson, Keith W. (Folder 118, Box 2)
  - Johnston, C.R. (Folder 119, Box 2)
  - Johnston, Eric (Folder 120, Box 2)
  - Johnstone, Dean (Folder 121, Box 2)
  - Joint Committee on the Economic Report (Folder 122, Box 2)
  - Jones, Martin V. (Folder 123, Box 2)
  - Journal of Accounting (Folder 124, Box 2)
  - Journal of the American Statistical Association (Folder 125, Box 2)
  - Journal of Business of University Chicago- Duddy, Edward A. (Folder 126, Box 2)
  - Journal of Commerce (Folder 127, Box 2)
  - The Journal of Economic History (Folder 128, Box 2)
  - The Journal of Political Economy (Folder 129, Box 2)
  - Joy, Aryness (Folder 130, Box 2)
  - Judd, F.M. (Folder 131, Box 2)
  - J- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 132, Box 2)
  - J- Miscellaneous 1932-34 (Folder 133, Box 2)
  - Kaplan, A.D.H. (Folder 134, Box 2)
  - Kapp, K.Wm. (Folder 135, Box 2)
  - Karsten, Karl (Folder 136, Box 2)
  - Keim, Walter G. (Folder 137, Box 2)
  - Keirstead, B.S. (Folder 138, Box 2)
  - Keiser, Norman F. (Folder 139, Box 2)
  - Kellett, William P. (Folder 140, Box 2)
  - Kellogg, Lester S. (Folder 141, Box 2)
  - Kemmerer, Donald L. (Folder 142, Box 2)
  - Kemp, Arthur (Folder 143, Box 2)
  - Kennedy, John (Folder 144, Box 2)
  - Kessler, David (Folder 145, Box 2)
  - Keuffel and Esser Co. (Folder 146, Box 2)
  - Keyserling, Leon H. (Folder 147, Box 2)
  - Kilberg, Edward J. (Folder 148, Box 2)
  - Killough, Hugh B. (Folder 149, Box 2)
  - Kincaid, E.A. (Folder 150, Box 2)
  - Kindahl, James K. (Folder 151, Box 2)
  - King, G.H. (Folder 152, Box 2)
  - King, Willford I. (Folder 153, Box 2)
  - Kneeland, Hildegarde (Folder 154, Box 2)
  - Knight, Frank H. (Folder 155, Box 2)
  - Konijn, H.S. (Folder 156, Box 2)
  - Kreps, Theodore J. (Folder 157, Box 2)
  - Kuhn, James W. (Folder 158, Box 2)
  - Kutish, John L. (Folder 159, Box 2)
  - Kunin, Ida (Folder 160, Box 2)
  - Kuznets, Simon (Folder 161, Box 2)
  - K- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 162, Box 2)
  - K- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 163, Box 2)
  - K- Miscellaneous 1932-53 (Folder 164, Box 2)
  - Lam, Midred (Folder 165, Box 2)
  - Landis, James M. (Folder 166, Box 2)
  - Lange, Oscar (Folder 167, Box 2)
  - Lanston, Aubrey G. (Folder 168, Box 2)
  - Lassins, Eldred G. (Folder 169, Box 2)
  - Leavens, Dicksen H. (Folder 170, Box 2)
  - Lederen, Emil (Folder 171, Box 2)
  - Lederer, Walther (Folder 172, Box 2)
  - Leffingwell R.C. (Folder 173, Box 2)
  - Leonard, William R. (Folder 174, Box 2)
  - Lee, Maurice W. (Folder 175, Box 2)
  - Lernar, Abba P. (Folder 176, Box 2)
  - Lerner, Eugene M. (Folder 177, Box 2)
  - Lewis, Ben (Folder 178, Box 2)
  - The Library of Congress (Folder 179, Box 2)
  - Murray, Lincoln D. (Folder 180, Box 2)
  - Lindeman, John (Folder 181, Box 2)
  - Lindolm, Richard W. (Folder 182, Box 2)
  - Linnenberg, Clen C., Jr. (Folder 183, Box 2)
  - Lintner, John (Folder 184, Box 2)
  - Livingston, J.A (Folder 185, Box 2)
  - Livingston, Morris S. (Folder 186, Box 2)
  - Lombard, Norman (Folder 187, Box 2)
  - Long, Clarence D. (Folder 188, Box 2)
  - Lorwin, Louis (Folder 189, Box 2)
  - Lovejoy, A. (Folder 190, Box 2)
    Also includes correspondence from Jan Tinbergen.
  - Lubin, Isador (Folder 191, Box 2)
  - Lucking, William A. (Folder 192, Box 2)
  - Luedicke, H.E. (Folder 193, Box 2)
  - Lutz, Friedrick A. (Folder 194, Box 2)
  - L- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 195, Box 2)
  - L- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 196, Box 2)
  - L- Miscellaneous 1932-54 (Folder 197, Box 2)
  - Macaulay, Fred R. (Folder 198, Box 2)
  - MacDonald, R.A. (Folder 199, Box 2)
  - MacDonald, R.C. (Folder 200, Box 2)
  - Machlup, Fritz (Folder 201, Box 2)
  - Mack, Ruth P. (Folder 202, Box 2)
  - Macmillan Co. (Folder 203, Box 2)
  - Magnusson, Leifur (Folder 204, Box 2)
  - Mann, Fritz Karl (Folder 205, Box 2)
  - Marget, Arthur W. (Folder 206, Box 2)
  - Marshall, Leon C. (Folder 207, Box 2)
  - Marshak, Jacob (Folder 208, Box 2)
  - Marthin, Robert (Folder 209, Box 2)
  - Martin, Thomas P. (Folder 210, Box 2)
  - Martin, William McChesney, Jr. (Folder 211, Box 2)
  - Mason, Edward S. (Folder 212, Box 2)
  - Matherly, Walter J. (Folder 213, Box 2)
  - Matthews, C.A. (Folder 214, Box 2)
  - McEwan, Robert J. (Folder 215, Box 2)
  - McGraw-Hill Publishing Co. Inc. (Folder 216, Box 2)
  - McKean, Ronald W. (Folder 217, Box 2)
  - McKinley, George Wells (Folder 218, Box 2)
  - McKinley, Gordon (Folder 219, Box 2)
  - Mc Lachlen, Archibald (Folder 220, Box 2)
  - Mc Queen, C.A. (Folder 221, Box 2)
  - Meigs, James A. (Folder 222, Box 2)
  - Mendershausen, Horst (Folder 223, Box 2)
  - Merrill, Charles E. (Merrill Center for Economics) (Folder 224, Box 2)
  - Mills, A.L., Jr. (Folder 225, Box 2)
  - Mints, Lloyd W. (Folder 226, Box 2)
  - Moffitt, C.D. (Folder 227, Box 2)
  - Molodovsky, Nicholos (Folder 228, Box 2)
  - Moody's Investors Service (Folder 229, Box 2)
  - Moore, Arthur L. (Folder 230, Box 2)
  - Morrison, Edward B. (NY Public Library) (Folder 231, Box 2)
  - Morrison, George R. (Folder 232, Box 2)
  - Morton, William (Folder 233, Box 2)
  - Mosak, Jacob L. (Folder 234, Box 2)
  - Maulton, Harold (Folder 235, Box 2)
  - Motlow, Thomas (Folder 236, Box 2)
  - Moynahan, John J. (Folder 237, Box 2)
  - Moyer, Fred W. (Folder 238, Box 2)
  - Murphy, Henry C. (Folder 239, Box 2)
  - Murray, James E. (Folder 240, Box 2)
  - Musgraue, Richard A. (Folder 241, Box 2)
  - Myers, Howard (Folder 242, Box 2)
  - Myers, William I. (Folder 243, Box 2)
  - M- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 244, Box 2)
  - M- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 245, Box 2)
  - M- Miscellaneous 1932-41 (Folder 246, Box 2)
  - Nadler, Marcus (Folder 247, Box 2)
  - Nadler, Paul (Folder 248, Box 2)
  - Nagendren, C. (Folder 249, Box 2)
  - Nathan, Robert (Folder 250, Box 2)
  - National Association of Mutual Savings Banks (Folder 251, Box 2)
  - National Industrial Conference Board (Folder 252, Box 2)
  - National Resources Committee Consumer Expenditures in the U.S., etc. (Folder 253, Box 2)
  - Nelson, James (Folder 254, Box 2)
  - Newbury, Frank D. (Folder 255, Box 2)
  - N.Y. Stock Exchange (Folder 256, Box 2)
  - N.Y. Times (Folder 257, Box 2)
  - N.Y. World Telegram (Folder 258, Box 2)
  - Nolle, William J. (Folder 259, Box 2)
  - Norcross, H.C. (Folder 260, Box 2)
  - Nortman, Bernard P. (Folder 261, Box 2)
  - Norton, Edward Lee (Folder 262, Box 2)